Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Choco Brownie
Extreme Blizzard. Let me show you how to
make it. In your pint, you're going to
combine 400 g of a fat-free high protein
milk, about a teaspoon of vanilla bean
paste, some sweetener, some salt, some
zantham gum. You guys know this recipe
by now. I've made it dozens of times.
Then you can just blend that all up and
throw in the freezer for about 16 hours.
Take it out, run under hot water for
about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. Now, the star of this recipe
are the mix-ins. So, we are using two of
what are, in my opinion, the best
protein snacks in the game right now.
The Horbles Twles chocolate bars and the
Alpha Prime Bites protein brownies. This
is an insane combination and adds almost
15 g of protein. Back to the ice cream,
though. We're going to take that out.
It's probably going to be pretty
powdery, so you can just scrape down the
sides with a butter knife and then throw
it back in the cream on the respin
setting. After the respin, it should be
looking pretty good. So, you can now go
ahead and smooth out the top and then
top it with all of those mixins and then
just mix them in by hand. I actually
find that it works way better than the
mixin feature.